Guide to the J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers, 1964-1968
Department of Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1966-1967
  - Correspondence: O - Z (1966 - 1967) (Box 9)
Pucinski, Roman C. 2 68
Reagan, Ronald (1911 -) 1 46 2 44 4 36
Redeker, Harry E. 2 33
Reith, Edward 1 31
Rhodes, John J. (1916 -) 1 66
Riddell, Robert E. 1 1
Rivers, Lucius Mendel (1905 -) 2 65
Sanders, Ira T. 1 53
Schacht, Henry 1 2
Seagraves, Roy W. 3 10
Shipman, Carl L. 2 11
Shriver, Sargent (1915 -) 6 32 6 33
Springer, William L. 2 73 3 2 3 3
Staggers, Harley O. 2 73
Stewart, William H. 2 4
Talcott, Burt L. 1 10
Taylor, W. Allen 1 11
Teague, Olin Earl (1910 -) 3 24
Tenzer, Herbert 5 24
Tooker, John S. 1 18
Tucker, William H. 2 73
Udall, Stewart R. (1920 -) 2 53
Utt, James B. (1899 -) 2 12
Van Deerlin, Lionel 5 38
Whittier, James L. 5 23
Willis, Edwin E. (1904 -) 1 74
Wilson, Charles H. 1 51 3 9
Young, Crawford 1 11 1 12
Zablocki, Clement J. 2 26